ryanleeinnercircle.com 2011-12-17

# Ryan Lee Inner Circle

> **Privacy**
> 
> Effective Date: September, 2011
> 
> The following Privacy Policy governs the online information collection practices of Ozworth, LLC d/b/  
>  a "r yanleeinner cir cle.com" ("we" or "us"). Specifically, it outlines the types of information that we gather  
>  about you while you are using the r yanleeinner cir cle.com website (the "Site"), and the ways in which we  
>  use this information. This Privacy Policy, including our children's privacy statement, does not apply to any  
>  information you may provide to us or that we may collect offline and/or through other means (for example,  
>  at a live event, via telephone, or through the mail).
> 
> Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting and using the Site, you agree that your use of our Site,  
>  and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy. Because the Web is an evolving medium,  
>  we may need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, in which case we'll post the changes  
>  to this Privacy Policy on this website and update the Effective Date of the policy to reflect the date of the  
>  changes. By continuing to use the Site after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as  
>  modified.
> 
> How We Collect and Use Infor mation
> 
> We may collect and store personal or other information that you voluntarily supply to us online while using  
>  the Site (e.g., while on the Site or in responding via email to a feature provided on the Site). nanocontunuity  
>  only contacts individuals who specifically request that we do so or in the event that they have signed up  
>  to receive our free newsletters or have purchased one of our products. Ryanleeinnercircle.com collects  
>  personally identifying information from our users during online registration and online purchasing.  
>  Generally, this information includes name and e-mail address for registration to receive our free  
>  newsletters and name, postal address, and credit card information when purchasing our products. All of this  
>  information is provided to us by you.
> 
> We also collect and store information that is generated automatically as you navigate online through the  
>  Site. For example, we may collect information about your computer's connection to the Internet, which  
>  allows us, among other things, to improve the delivery of our web pages to you and to measure traffic  
>  on the Site. We also may use a standard feature found in browser software called a "cookie" to enhance  
>  your experience with the Site. Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your hard drive  
>  for record-keeping purposes. By showing how and when visitors use the Site, cookies help us deliver  
>  advertisements, identify how many unique users visit us, and track user trends and patterns. They also  
>  prevent you from having to re-enter your preferences on certain areas of the Site where you may have  
>  entered preference information before. The Site also may use web beacons (single-pixel graphic files also  
>  known as "transparent GIFs") to access cookies and to count users who visit the Site or open HTML-  
>  formatted email messages.
> 
> We use the information we collect from you while you are using the Site in a variety of ways, including  
>  using the information to customize features and advertising that appear on the Site. We also may provide  
>  your information to third parties, such as service providers, contractors, and advertisers, for a variety of  
>  purposes. Unless you inform us in accordance with the process described below, we reserve the right to  
>  use, and to disclose to third parties, all of the information collected from and about you while you are  
>  using the Site in any way and for any purpose, such as to enable us or a third party to provide you with  
>  information about products and services. If you do not wish your information to be used for these purposes,  
>  you must send a letter to the Online Privacy Coordinator whose address is listed at the end of this Privacy  
>  Policy requesting to be taken off any lists of information that may be used for these purposes or that may be  
>  given or sold to third-parties.
> 
> Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily make your personal information available for viewing  
>  by third parties online – for example on message boards, web logs, through email, or in chat areas –  
>  that information can be seen, collected and used by others besides us. We cannot be responsible for any  
>  unauthorized third-party use of such information.
> 
> Some of our third-party advertisers and ad servers that place and present advertising on the Site also  
>  may collect information from you via cookies, web beacons or similar technologies. These third-party  
>  advertisers and ad servers may use the information they collect to help present their advertisements, to help  
>  measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness, or for other purposes. The use and collection of  
>  your information by these third-party advertisers and ad servers is governed by the relevant third-party's
> 
> advertisers and ad servers may be different from ours. If you have any concerns about a third party's use  
>  of cookies or web beacons or use of your information, you should visit that party's website and review its  
>  privacy policy.
> 
> The Site also includes links to other websites and provides access to products and services offered by third  
>  parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase third-party  
>  products or services through the Site, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy  
>  of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services.
> 
> We may also make some content, products and services available through our Site through cooperative  
>  relationships with third-party providers, where the brands of our provider partner appear on the Site in  
>  connection with such content, products and/or services. We may share with our provider partner any  
>  information you provide, or that is collected, in the course of visiting any pages that are made available in  
>  cooperation with our provider partner. In some cases, the provider partner may collect information from  
>  you directly, in which cases the privacy policy of our provider partner may apply to the provider partner's  
>  use of your information. The privacy policy of our provider partners may differ from ours. If you have any  
>  questions regarding the privacy policy of one of our provider partners, you should contact the provider  
>  partner directly for more information.
> 
> Be aware that we may occasionally release information about our visitors when release is appropriate to  
>  comply with law or to protect the rights, property or safety of users of the Site or the public.
> 
> Please also note that as our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that we  
>  sell some or all of our assets, or one or more of our websites is acquired by another company, information  
>  about our users may be among the transferred assets.
> 
> Children's Pr ivacy Statement
> 
> This children's privacy statement explains our practices with respect to the online collection and use of  
>  personal information from children under the age of thirteen, and provides important information regarding  
>  their rights under federal law with respect to such information.
> 
> This Site is not directed to children under the age of thirteen and we do NOT knowingly collect  
>  personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Site. We  
>  screen users who wish to provide personal information in order to prevent users under the age of  
>  thirteen from providing such information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received  
>  personally identifiable information from a user under the age of thirteen as part of the Site, we will  
>  delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain  
>  prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from  
>  children under the age of thirteen as part of the Site.
> 
> Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of  
>  thirteen as part of the Site, we also do NOT knowingly distribute such information to third parties.
> 
> We do NOT knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen to publicly post or otherwise  
>  distribute personally identifiable contact information through the Site.
> 
> Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of  
>  thirteen as part of the Site, we do NOT condition the participation of a child under thirteen in the  
>  Site's online activities on providing personally identifiable information.
> 
> How do we stor e your infor mation?
> 
> Your information is stored at the list server that delivers Ryanleeinnercircle.com newsletters. Your  
>  information can only be accessed by those who help manage those lists in order to deliver e-mail to those  
>  who would like to receive Ryanleeinnercircle.com newsletters.
> 
> All of the newsletters or emails that are sent to you by Nanocontinutiy.com include an unsubscribe link  
>  in them. You can remove yourself at any time from our newsletters or mailing list by clicking on the  
>  unsubscribe link. You can also contact us at ryanlee.com/support to change your information at any time.
> 
> Disclaimer
> 
> Although it is highly unlikely, This policy may be changed at any time at our discretion. If we should
> 
> update this policy, we will post the updates to this page on our Website.
> 
> If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy please contact our team at ryanlee.com/  
>  support
